{
    "subject": "resource/Ferret_Music",
    "predicate": "ontology/distributingLabel",
    "object": "resource/Alternative_Distribution_Alliance",
    "human_readable": "Ferret Music is distributed by Alternative Distribution Alliance.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9609590172767639,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Ferret Music and Alternative Distribution Alliance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9079761505126953,
            "question": "Who distributes music by Ferret Music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.899728536605835,
            "question": "Is Alternative Distribution Alliance involved in music distribution?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8809235692024231,
            "question": "Which music label's music is distributed by Alternative Distribution Alliance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.813409149646759,
            "question": "Does Ferret Music have its own distribution system?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8063568472862244,
            "question": "What kind of music does Ferret Music typically distribute?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7730516791343689,
            "question": "Can you name other music labels distributed by Alternative Distribution Alliance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7359569668769836,
            "question": "What is the name of the company that distributes Ferret Music's music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6528078317642212,
            "question": "What type of company is Alternative Distribution Alliance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6336706280708313,
            "question": "How does Alternative Distribution Alliance help musicians reach their audience?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ferret Music is distributed by Alternative Distribution Alliance.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6959_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of company is Alternative Distribution Alliance?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6959_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the company that distributes Ferret Music's music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6959_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name other music labels distributed by Alternative Distribution Alliance?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6959_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6959_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6959_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6959_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6959_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6959_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6959_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6959_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6959_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6959_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6959_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all three documents mention that Ferret Music is currently distributed by Fontana Distribution, Alternative Distribution Alliance and eOne Music, which supports the triple that Ferret Music is distributed by Alternative Distribution Alliance."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this statement. Specifically, document `29.txt` and `72.txt` mention that Warner Music Group's Alternative Distribution Alliance acquired a stake in Ferret Music in August 2006 and is currently distributing it along with Fontana Distribution and eOne Music."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}